{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In &quot;Undertale&quot;, how many main endings are there?","correct_answer":"3","incorrect_answers":["2","5","13"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In the game series &quot;The Legend of Zelda&quot;, what was the first 3D game?","correct_answer":"Ocarina of Time","incorrect_answers":["Majora&#039;s Mask","A Link to the Past","The Wind Waker"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"Which of these online games was originally named LindenWorld in it&#039;s early development?","correct_answer":"SecondLife","incorrect_answers":["ActiveWorlds","IMVU","HabboHotel"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In the Halo series, what fleet was Thel &#039;Vadam supreme commander of before being branded an Arbiter?","correct_answer":"Fleet of Particular Justice","incorrect_answers":["Fleet of Sacred Consecration","Fleet of Furious Redemption","Fleet of Righteous Vigilance"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The end credits sequence in Grand Theft Auto 5 is over half an hour long.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which water-type Pok&eacute;mon starter was introduced in the 4th generation of the series?","correct_answer":"Piplup","incorrect_answers":["Totodile","Oshawott","Mudkip"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In &quot;PAYDAY 2&quot;, what weapon has the highest base weapon damage on a per-shot basis?","correct_answer":"HRL-7","incorrect_answers":["Heavy Crossbow","Thanatos .50 cal","Broomstick Pistol"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"Which of these characters wasn&#039;t a villian in Club Penguin?","correct_answer":"The Director","incorrect_answers":["Herbert P. Bear","Tusk","Ultimate Proto-Bot 10000"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In &quot;The Witness&quot;, how many lasers must be activated to get into the mountain area?","correct_answer":"7","incorrect_answers":["8","5","12"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Divinity: Original Sin II, what is the name of the skeletal origin character?","correct_answer":"Fane","incorrect_answers":["Lohse","The Red Prince","There are no skeletal origin characters"]}]}